http://www.bssa.org.uk/terms.php

Terms and Conditions
BRITISH STAINLESS STEEL ASSOCIATIONMaking the Most of Stainless Steel
Contact
Members Area
Select quick linkMember ListRelated OrganisationsSpecial GradesStainless Steel CorrosionSurface Finishes
GO
GO
BRITISH STAINLESS STEEL ASSOCIATIONMaking the Most of Stainless Steel
Contact
Members Area
Select quick linkMember ListRelated OrganisationsSpecial GradesStainless Steel CorrosionSurface Finishes
GO
GO
Toggle navigation
HomeAbout BSSATechnical HelpFind a SupplierShopNewsTrainingEventsBSSA MembersAffiliate MembersContact Us
HomeTerms & Conditions
Featured Articles & PublicationsStainless Steel Grades DatasheetsBS 6744 2016 (May) Update - Stainless Steel Bars, Reinforcement of ConcreteAvailability of Stainless Steel GradesGetting the Best out of Stainless SteelSpecial Grades of Stainless Steel - Where to Find ThemDuplex Stainless Steels - A Simplified GuideFabricating Duplex Stainless SteelThe Then and Now of ElectropolishingStructural Sections in Stainless SteelStainless steel fastenersEuropean Standards - Referenced Standards for Stainless Steel ProductsEuropean EN Standard Grade Summary
Terms and Conditions
The Website
Every effort is made to ensure that the information on this website is regularly checked and kept up to date. However, no liability can be held for the completeness, actuality and accuracy of the information within these pages. The access to and use of the website as well as all information contained or referred to therein lies in the sole responsibility of the user.
The contents of linked pages are not a component of this website. No responsibility or liability can be held for the contents or changes to contents of linked pages.
The use of any part of the contents of this website, in particular its reproduction, distribution or transmission, requires the prior permission of the British Stainless Steel Association.
Privacy Policy/Notice
General
Our Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide directly to us or via the BSSA website or the Stainless Steel Advisory Service. Whenever you use the BSSA website or the Stainless Steel Advisory Service, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy/Notice.
Ways that we collect and retain information
Some areas of the site require you to submit information about yourself in order to receive information about our products and services. Some of this information may be personal (information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, job title etc.).
We only collect such information when you choose to supply it to us.
Please note that details about enquirers to the Stainless Steel Advisory Service (name, company, location, email address and a record of the enquiry and advice / guidance given) are recorded on a database, a summary of which is made available to Association member companies who may follow up enquiries by offering products and services related to the enquiry. We believe that this is a helpful service of legitimate interest to enquirers, but if you prefer that your details and the details of your enquiry are not made available to Association member companies, please clearly indicate this with your enquiry.
Typically, individuals data is retained for the current and the previous calendar years or, in other circumstances, until the individual unsubscribes from a service. Data regarding companies who are members of the Association, along with certain employees, are held on a “Legitimate Interest” basis to allow us to provide the agreed membership services. This basis is also relevant to individuals who attend or purchase training courses, purchase publications or attend events.
An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), so you can access the internet. It is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address is dynamic (changing each time you connect to the internet), rather than static (unique to a particular user's computer). We may use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, and to administer and improve the site.
Web Statistics
We use log files generated by our web servers to analyse site usage and statistics but the files do not identify any personal information. Log file analysis helps us to understand usage patterns on our website and to make improvements to our service.
Disclosure
Except as otherwise stated, we may use information you provide via this site to improve the content, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for research purposes, and for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.
We do not disclose any information you provide via the site or the Stainless Steel Advisory Service to any third parties unless you give us permission to do so.
Links to other websites
This site may contain links and references to other websites. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites and we encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every website you visit.
Disclaimer
Copyright © 2018 British Stainless Steel Association. All rights reserved.
No part of this publication may be reproduced or transmitted by any means, electronic, mechanical, (including photocopying), recording or by any information storage and retrieval system, without prior permission from the copyright owners.
BSSA disclaims all responsibility and liability (including negligence) in relation to information on or accessible from this site.
Your Agreement
The use of our website and the Stainless Steel Advisory Service constitutes your agreement with these terms of use.
Individuals have a right to complain to the Information Commissioners Office if they feel that there is a problem with the way in which their data is handled.
Policy Changes
If our terms of use change in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.top
Site MapTerms & ConditionsMembers AreaCookie Policy
Office and Postal Address: BSSA, The Innovation Centre, 217 Portobello, Sheffield S1 4DP
Registered Office: Pegasus House, 463A Glossop Road, Sheffield S10 2QD
Tel: +44 (0)114 5518170.    |     Email: admin@bssa.org.uk
Copyright © 2018 British Stainless Steel Association
web design sheffield by Llama Digital
